PETER LU

(647)-456-4707 **peterlu94@gmail.com**

Extracurricular

Computer Science Frosh Fall 2014 || Frosh Leader University of Toronto

Computer Science Student Union

2014/2016 | General Council University of Toronto

Coursework

- Data Structures and Analysis
- Introduction to Machine Learning
- Introduction to Artificial Intelligence
- Introduction to Databases
- Introduction to Software Engineering
- Introduction to Neural Networks

Profile

Software engineer with experience developing in object-oriented languages such as Python and Java, MVC architectures such as Flask, with a focus in data processing and analysis. Also have experience with writing test suites and automated testing.

Experience

Software Developer Intern, Acuity Ads Inc. - May 2015 - Sept 2015

- Managed and performed tests concerning Acuity's back-end RTB (Realtime bidding) network, and the front-end trading platform console.
- Contributed in developing the internal test client to perform validation tests in Java using the Spring framework.

Global Network Support Intern, Bank of Nova Scotia — May 2014 - Sept 2014

- Assisted the GNS team in handling and solving issues regarding network stability.
- Conducted analytics on network nodes using the SolarWinds platform to identify stress points in the network.
- Managed and updated server network documents and diagrams concerning serviced Caribbean countries.

Education

University of Toronto — B.Sc in Computer Science, Expected June 2017

Skills

Highly Experienced In: Python, Java, Git

Experienced In: Javascript, HTML/CSS, SQL, C, Flask, Ruby, Selenium

Projects

Housing Analysis-CA | Python, Flask, HTML, CSS — Feb 2017 - Present Simple web application written in Python and Flask to analyze housing data for major Canadian cities using Pandas and NumPy Python libraries. It extract insights such as interval growth over a time period and differences on various indicators over the regions, as well as a simple regression model to predict future house prices.

Aquarium | Javascript, JQuery, Node.js - Jan 2015 - April 2015

An improved, user-friendly shell emulator written in Node.js, serving as a fully functional system shell with additional features such as command autocompletion, inline quick documentation, and a sidebar for verbose TL;DR documentation.